so I gotta wait for this thing to
calibrate
so y'all know the craziest thing about
0.3 0.4 0.4 your yawn and I can't show
you my yawn right now because it's
specially modified but your yawn we
flipped upside down so if you unscrew
the screws from the top and unscrew the
screws on the bottom you can switch the
position of the two places you can
switch the position of the two places
and then you can uh speaking of bums we
got more right here we're gonna cruise
past it yep boom yeah so I got a
calibrate so that means I got a drive
above 45 miles an hour it's a little bit
like speed here unfortunately the new
version will not zero point four point
four will not be shipping with the new
calibration I mean you can blame the
calibration team for that and we don't
blame anybody there's no blame everybody
loves everybody because it's a beautiful
world but what's important is zero point
four point four we'll have some of the
best stuff and one of the fate my
favorite feature is zero point four
point four is I'm being recorded right
now by the front camera mom it's
optional you can turn it on or off your
yawns also upside down which allows the
front camera to see the driver much
better it kind of just makes the
experience just kind of makes the
experience better so I can't engage yet
because calibration is not finished so
we're gonna go on the highway and hope
it calibrates
but yeah we can uh we can take questions
any any questions for this this dopey
Tuesday show you guys well I can't show
you the e on I can't show you the Ian
because it's a secret e on secret e on
I'm doing a little bit more than testing
each and release Friday looking at
Friday when will I shave Friday Friday
last stuffs happening Friday big big
event
why recording the driver so this is our
push towards eventual driver monitoring
for safety as our system gets better and
better and better you know we're gonna
need to start making sure yeah chef
pleasantly updated to you know you know
this time I always say it but this time
I'm serious
shift+ will be updated what's the
five-year vision for coming do I look
like the kind of guy who has vision I
don't even shave it's good damn Friday
just like just like Rebecca Black said a
new model nope there won't be a banana
that's a new calibration before new
model guys new calibration almost is
ready to ship that will ship probably in
0 for 5 but um a bunch more UI
improvements we're trying to make this
like a nice so gold star stuff is
already live gulf try stuffs already
live we just haven't built the dashboard
for you guys to see it yeah we have a
pipeline stage internally which runs and
checks if you've met your routes gold
star unfortunately it all the way tell
you yet I am driving here with a grape
and I can show you my grape and I can't
show you the e on its secret but grape
and I can definitely show you look at
that great panel what a nice great panel
alright
recording for safety feature yeah
recording is a safety feature no so we
don't actually have any of the detection
yet what we're gonna do is we're gonna
collect data I mean it's easy to write
an attack here to see if the driver has
the rise in the road but we want to
figure out what policy we want to put on
that detector and that's kind of what
we're gonna crowdsource
calibration work in this thing
how does the camera being offset
slightly affect driving quality all of
the flip we've corrected for it 0:44
will include front camera uploads
absolutely we have a way to view them
but they're getting uploaded
yeah the e on camera we very we've
already corrected for therefore the
six-inch things don't worry about that
it's a little rainy here in San
Francisco today
you said you collected he oh I'm nothing
like Zuckerberg man you can change the
difference yeah I'll tell you the real
difference to Nelson Facebook right
Facebook is trying to maximize
engagement for you we're trying to
maximize engagement for the machine our
dream product is a product you put in
the car and never think about we're not
gonna pressure you to drive more we're
not gonna send you an email hey your
friends have said you haven't driven in
seven days consider driving consider how
Ashley would feel right I feel Facebook
is emotionally manipulative and evil and
sucks testifying in Congress right now
no that's going but you know I would
never do things like that right we're
we're a product like you buy it for
utility right we're we're a lot more
like like an Amazon or a Microsoft or an
Apple I'm not really like a Facebook or
Google all right what am I doing with
your data just making the models better
man I don't know I'm too lazy to sell
your data I'm too lazy I'm too lazy what
I have to do business development with
people it just sounds like a lot of
effort I have to transfer the data have
to make a portal it's too much effort we
use it to make the experience better for
you guys no I stated my facebook a long
time ago
I believe in my facebook in 20
13 better year after I worked there I
know I know chef applause coming soon we
hired two more people for that team so
that's pretty exciting
new ship lasya douche ever fly settle at
they laugh
anything else what I'm talking about I
don't know guys just bought it on talk
to us go peace review a facebook
employment it's not a bad place to work
no so accepting face reporting is
completely optional it has nothing to do
with safety on what won't be optional is
when we ship the driver monitoring so
you don't have to like record your face
does the data will never be recorded but
we will run a neural net on it to
determine whether you're paying
attention no I'm in a Civic right now so
I don't need the pedal if you like
forefoot if you like four three two
you're gonna love for for what else is
new on for for just a whole lot of
stability fixes guys it should just be a
you know that's what the big big number
means what I think of D Central and I
don't know what that is what is d
Central and
sommore autofocus improvements two four
zero four fours come Friday what do I
think of Pied Piper
I think middle-out compression is gonna
change everything big architecture is
going to change everything
driver monitor will disengage quickly
upon driver distraction but as an
advantage to that you don't have to deal
with the six minute timer anymore as
long as you're paying attention it won't
time out once we shut the driver
distracted alerts
and we'll be using so it won't be out in
0 for 4 but when we ship new calibration
new calibration will live on the DSP you
guys who got the DSP lurking don't tell
anyone does the new model use mapping no
no no guys because everything takes a
long-ass time you know has it been a
long-ass time since we did mapping
periscopes not really oh man look at all
this traffic on the way back
it is calibrating one person Wow
calibration sucks I'm gonna have to
drive all the way to Mountain View for
this thing to calibrate oh it is
exciting though Oh 2% I haven't
calibrated an open pilot and so long
this is a new device Oh free the DSP Sh
well I mean you know maybe it's time
favored you free the DSP maybe we should
free the DSP how does the model predict
the road Oh how does it do that I'll use
the maps
none of that stuff shipping it works but
it doesn't think of the shaft yeah
eventually
everything takes forever it just takes
forever to build anything guys
oh man this is terrible you're telling
me I have to drive while it calibrates
these brutal calibration shouldn't take
so long it takes so long uh uh you know
I'm not gonna say anything bad you know
it's just it was written a long time ago
before we understood everything about
computer vision before we all got PhDs
in computer vision we have much better
calibration but it's only internal but
it will ship soon got a ship it got a
ship you get put on the device and we're
gonna be used the DSP for that well
we're gonna ship something called orb D
or 'buddy is gonna compute great orb
features right there on your DSP only at
11% this is terrible
it looks calibrated - sorry guys
user-experience got to get better yeah
for diffusion on nobody's done shit
how'd y'all get the DSP I used to be
when I was 22 I was probably the best
hacker alive I'm not anymore but you
know I get still I get ESP right it's
worse than this traffic yeah yeah no
come on open pilot Oh 13%
what's the calibration for it figures
out where your cameras mounted with
respect to your car so in order to like
drive the car we have to know where to
go guys it's all like foggy here too
it's pretty cool I'll flip you around so
you can say the DSB is just another
that's what my young seeing right now
guys I can't show you that yell because
it's a secret specially on but uh oh
it's bad foggy is 16% oh my god this is
really gonna take forever
no you don't need to recalibrate this is
just this is just because I'm on a new
device only if you buy new devices we
need to read
you're currently trading a depth on how
you trying again what's a channel
five miles oh man this is brutal
I just wanted to casually go out and
test open Pilon humans go peeing while
you're training definite what one plus
five no no one plus five you can't have
the secret eh I can't show you this
secret secret yeah there's a secret code
name to it as a code name that's pretty
cool you get the Z distance from the
camera what do you mean how do you get
the Z distance in the cavity back oh man
calibration takes days
really it you shouldn't have to take
this long Oh Oh terrible experience
Oh oh you have the death net from unity
oh so you're not just gonna kill the
Kamera I understand okay so it's not a
real camera there's a civics probably
the best car for a pilot show Honda by
Toyota new face filters on comics back
whose face filters I know what that
means
to the road guys
like the phone is mounted almost like in
my line of sight
I'm using a hands-free phone like I got
both hands I can't really keep them off
a wheel because all piles only 33% is
terrible it's a terrible experience you
guys I am gonna email support and
comment on the eye and I'll tell them
that calibration is taking way too long
and I'm very frustrated very frustrated
guys know I hate calibration takes too
much time I agree I've never really
experienced your pain guys but like now
I have we don't gonna have to sit in
this traffic on the way home no I've
asked her a refund support Akari i'm
viviane my eon takes too long to
calibrate i want a refund largest prize
ever 150k 150 k for my chrome full stack
trafficker 38% boys 38% it might not
like I might press the button and it
might not even engaged to be honest this
is a very untested experimental secret
Eon we're hiring new we're hiring new
support representatives we're hiring
were hiring Zoe and Zelda I'm talking
about new funding Shh
who talks that new funding okay if I
reporters all day yesterday and I didn't
pick up cuz I'm like no coming guys calm
is kind of a stealth mode you guys are
kind of in on the secret
and he hints on new wheel it's not cool
guys it's not cool it's really not cool
it's shitty yacht you don't want one of
these you really tell it it's worse than
the Aeon do you have well right now
anyway it might get better but you know
it's a long time right now it's not
custom hardware
so we'll drive down to San Jose while it
calibrates we'll drive back with new
calibration
which pretty dim - yeah
3a is hard but yeah we should use the
tx2 for a new who said anything about a
new hardware platform new funding new
hardware platform it's actually almost
like that it's not Nokia it's funny it's
funny though
yeah it works the traffic laughs yes yes
it works with traffic lights
51% oh my god this takes years
all right we're gonna we're gonna make
calibration good when I get home I know
all the bus keys are running out no no
Pete - guys are too smart can you have
an option to uninstall - no no options
you know support company all right no
you want to install it go in SSH NPM
uninstalled you can understand the
hesitation about what fine good what's
good nothing's good it's all shit yeah
everything's great purse I love the
world and I love life the world is a
beautiful place
added to for for what no no options no
buttons no you give a user button no
presently you don't want to they won't
press it when you want to that's the
button saying whatever that should be a
good slack my response whenever the
slack whenever someone's saying like
look we have a button to do access you
don't give users buttons I'll just stop
like oh something's really good the
stoplight is insanely good because we've
coated the locations in using about um
so we have some maps now we have some
maps we have the first bunch of maps of
San Francisco Logan Paul beads yo I
don't think I can connect to my phone of
course this car things unusable but I
would totally play the number song help
me help you right now
no I know the Logan fall songs yeah I'm
a little Oh gang member I love gangster
that's right
no I'm overlooking Paul on both songs
look all sellout
that's right but the Maverick merch
which I am wearing right now is the
softest wear to the game so does that do
we use semantically labeled of maps
auto-generated we use the same pipeline
we used to generate our training data
for the maps
and you guys probably don't even think
we have training data because there's
never any new bottles just Kali
that's Kali
alright guys I think it's about time we
turn around my calibrations at 74%
that's pretty good
this is so exciting though if I was a
new person getting this thing I would
expect wonderful things what's new in
four I mean I'm sorry I can't show you
guys this thing because it's a secret
Aeon but it's good it's just a lot of a
lot of polish a lot of Polish 0 for 4 is
going to be pushed to release so
remember how like the warrant release
push to release new for supports going
to release total focus has been largely
fixed so HDR is live 0:44 is going live
on Friday and will do new Scheffer plus
to a secret Aeon don't worry about the
secret the secret iana's is just get a
lot disagree to you it's a downgrade
from your car D but that's just why I
can't show you I don't know I just
didn't want to be alone on this drive
alone without for calibration so I
thought I'd bring Muskogee's with me
yeah 0 for 3 is released quality good
guys like 0 4 3 0 4 3 2 okay
counsel hierarchy CVP asked me I should
have the same DPS it said the gray
pattern pretty much I have the same like
chips that series
did you record Maps yes if you got a
grand Pantheon yes you absolutely
recorded max no no nothing ever gets
cheaper calm my things only get more
expensive do you guys know that pandas
used to be $88 so now they're $99 should
have bought a panda when they were 88
save that money now get on Black
Mountain Road yeah
all right calibrations at 90% this is
very exciting
I've never been so excited to get a new
product it's a u-blox m8o that's the
Highway Patrol I got a watch out now you
don't just not doing anything illegal
I'm an upstanding sense pig the $88
Pentastar nephew arey um though you guys
know the pandas aren't going on Amazon
that is happening
little bit of Tyre squeal off the line
there base station D is on holes cuz
it's not gonna make anything better
how you gonna market panda on Amazon
this is way better bros have you used
Cabana and then you bought an OPG and
you've used PI L 11 we don't believe in
marketing if you don't want it don't buy
it you know I think it's the best if I
could have bought cheap OBD dongles I
totally would have
instead of pandas if I could have not
made that and just watching fo BD
Dominus we're doing it right on the
merch we were already doing fulfillments
lianying it's good price on those
t-shirts at 20 bucks
I've new download video from your
chauffeur drives I think you can it's
kind of screen capture software now
we're gonna work on that every file you
upload to us okay let's download
oh it's calibrated what controls
mismatch what oh we're in controls
mismatch okay that's not great oh all
that work doesn't work restarting on
restart car guys I don't even have an e
on is it the e on I gotta restart
restart car I controls mismatch it says
take control immediately controls
mismatch guys I want a secret debug e on
and it sucks it's not even in the e on
ok that's how much it sucks
yep Wow okay you know it's good for
people to experience their own products
yeah I mean really support when I get
home I'm very upset
oh man I should show you guys begun I
wish I could show you the yen are you
using me only I'm not selling me out why
are you using because we're testing it I
don't know why it doesn't work he's done
a good job yep you talk to that shit I
did that once in the acura the acura
does not restart alright we will try we
will try rebooting the car we'll pull
over
we'll try rebooting the car yeah well I
missed that exit skyline Boulevard next
exit
cool skylight college skyline college
guys
Civic will restart when in neutral yeah
we're not trying it go will take Skyline
Drive up top that's kind of nice
it engages for a minute I really don't
even think this is caused by other
issues man
Zach
[Music]
in the toyota you can disable the cruise
and then you can restart the device oh
the drive constellation I don't know
Zuckerberg what's he's doing how's that
going I can't watch that I'm driving
it's live right now he's sweating
bullets now I wish you the best of luck
I mean guys you know if you don't like
Facebook at least like Facebook does
look good for the world he's testifying
in front of Congress Congress
you listen to it on CNN I heard didn't
really think news I don't watch CNN but
I've heard rumors that they're extremely
fake news I don't know if those Turner I
keep an open mind of a skeptic is the
earth flat
I'm a skeptic
Oh Honda Bosch is that shit working but
if that's working guys okay I will tell
you I will tell you since this periscope
it's been a terrible periscope I will
drop some who knowledge of a secret kama
product don't get cyclists and some
javelin cyclists I will drop some
knowledge Congress shit man this is not
a reflection on Americans as a whole
do not take Congress to reflect the good
people of the United States of America
no controls mismatched no all right now
I need to find a place to pull over on
this road actually tow supercruise on
this road and it didn't work no no it's
not the kama radar stock acc okay so you
got lateral only on the Boche it's
impossible to do the longitudinal if we
had vision only
bringing
no it controls it for like half a second
I don't understand what's going on
I feel unplug and replug the Panda
alright guys know the secret new product
you know no secret product now it'll do
it we'll do a real announcement
where are you co-pilot what's a co-pilot
oh why is no one else in the car alright
a red light alright let's reboot let's
reboot let's reboot now pull over to the
side here I don't have chrome boss just
me in the car
only on testing the new prototype yeah
and three but it makes a different noise
when it reboots because it's a prototype
secret Aeon
rebooting turn my hazard lights on
rebooting rebooting its booting booting
right because I have a grape and a tow
sitting by the side of a road where
people go fast as scary well the front
camera of HD I know doesn't have a GTR
god I gotta make work a little better at
night wrap no come on work work all
right it's booted starting up all the UI
crap let's go let's go I wish I could
show you guys the secret e on the secret
e on his monitoring know all the yawns
you guys this is flipping Deion's I'll
show you some flipping Deion's time
Chris how's the mapping going pretty
well
and that thing's pretty good you know
I didn't work at all okay the USB is
kind of janky on this prototype I think
that's the problem it's connected to the
Panda let's go
please keep hands on wheel be ready to
take over at any time love it alright
come on
engage Oh works it works yeah whoo oh
this one doesn't know that we have oh I
don't have upgraded torque on this whoa
I'm a pilot what's open pilot all right
guys let's shake no I can't show you
cause it's on the secret prototype
beyond whoa
secret prototype works whoo love it
whoever said booboo car that guy
Oh hitting the brakes oh what a good
prototype its prototypes I gotta keep my
hands by the wheel got a car in five
foot by the brake wheel
alright prototype ping-pong and getting
fixed we developed the prototype this
guy no it's not true
Eddie worked on it a bed one of our
other engineers worked on in a bed I
just came in to the car I put it in the
car
what's different about secret here it
sucks it's like in normally-on but
crappier I just know I'm not getting
increased torque because it doesn't know
that I'm gonna modify it Civic
whoo cruising through a red light right
now oh don't go there
all right
what talks about the prior right guys
you know what who would I be
won't tell you anything about it but we
will show you all the pilot there is
open pilot and it's driving yeah
this is the first time given on a new
secret prototype be on there like eons
but crappier because their secret
prototypes but it is notice how it is
upside down
notice how the fat parts over here and
the skinny parts over here you're
driving through the fog
of course it's a civic so I have full
stop and go this is open pilot that cut
out here we're good you like that look
at that triangle it looks secret no the
triangles gonna ship no hands are gonna
hand right here I mean I'm not you know
I don't need to it's doing itself but
just mess up you know no no no plenty
more OPP threes plenty more OPD threes
this is just a prototype but actually
unless you want to end up with one of
these player er today
it's not a 5t it is definitely not a 5t
notice rain effect that it doesn't care
what's OPG 3 I don't know what that
means
but you know this is the latest version
of all compiled and this is pretty good
I'm not very happy with this experience
look at the new UI look sick
yeah faster Excel from stop and it gets
fixed
mafic gold star when engaged or not
engaged don't care an app still look the
same no matter who's driving you are
looks fancy right that's zero point four
point four you guys really stuck around
so you know even though it's the secret
prototype it's really really low
visibility today I think I got a radar
that cuts right through that fog
nice to help a little on the sharp turn
we had the torque limit of the Civic
no no no it's not a Samsung what sensor
jeez our only phone we use all these
sensors in the car
as well as the phone and we also use a
grey panda check out a grape and all
right there
check out my antenna oh wow that is a
janky antenna mount I'm gonna go get in
gameplay we added some green color what
is this sorcery is a cell phone driving
a car guys that's no big deal
it's a cell phone driving a car
it's wrong here can't really see cuz the
fog
unless the Americans time
this one's a little junk here
so yeah this is this is not a neon if
you buy any on you'll have a actually a
much better experience of this this is a
janky scrap
I shouldn't insult it too much because
future he hunts may look like this I put
you guys back in the mouth
what is this explain answers it is open
pilot by common guy the only best free
open source car driver no it's it's an e
it's a neon guys it's a neon it's a
crappy Aeon it's a prototype beyond you
buy any on today you get the latest and
greatest a neon technology you buy this
eon you're like this is crappy you can't
buy this eon it's crappy and sold the
choice yeah check it or github
github.com / comment i / open pilot that
might go to the highway how much can we
vary by a best buy nope you know where
you can buy you go to shop calm or
dining I now it doesn't come with any
software that drives a car and yawns are
sold as dash cams they really are just
designed to be - cabs if you are crazy
and adventurous and want to go to github
and download open-source driving
software it might just run on that
dashcam but that is of course your
choice as a free individual in a free
country shop comma dot a yeah I go to
that store and then you two can have a
cell phone drive your car
is it a shaman dumps not shouting no no
no we're pushing nothing nothing don't
worry there's plenty of new updates to
come zero four four has this new
beautiful UI who what turns the wheel
we actually use magic I mean it's just
magic I don't know what else to say it's
like turning the wheel to go around this
turn yeah yeah I don't know if your car
has magic built into it that open
palette interfaces with magic and that's
how it turns means telekinesis yes open
pilot gr44
does require flipping your jaan model
based on to York someone asked me about
models model shop that I play shit I'll
show some more footage of this thing
I mean this is 0 for 4
I'm thank you for sticking around while
this calibrated and what I painfully had
to reboot my car all right we'll look
into why that happened but yeah so that
right there is a cell phone driving
their car zero point four point four
which is available for free and
opensource honor github at get our back
home slash coming on the show pilot
notice how you see that triangle there
so it's detecting the car in front of me
and it's gonna come to a nice smooth
stop we had an intern this summer right
a phenomenal model predictive controller
that's being used it the brakes probably
smoother than you can
it works on Honda's and Toyotas and this
is the year the Ford so it will be soon
to work on Ford's
it's glitching out a little distracted
by the time the software is running on
main yawns that bun you saw earlier was
probably not a software probably that's
why issue with center dividers and you
like Tessa's issue can I always pay
attention you know I don't know try it
post a comparison video you want this
for your rav4 rav4 is a great car to
install this and check it out look at
that look at how that path goes away man
this new UI looks good we hired a
designer almost a year ago now he's
absolutely crushing it a huge fan how
does it handle cyclists it doesn't you
handle cyclists
what's the device on the left of the
yeah oh that's a Rove Rove I don't know
Andy was trying doubt can ask me what he
thinks about this is open pilot this is
a cellphone driving a car sorry we're
not gonna say self-driving car anymore
we're gonna say driver assistance system
so I'm a driver
I'm in the driver's seat I'm legally in
control this vehicle at all times I'm
paying attention but as long as I'm
doing all those things from this device
right here this is a common AI beyond
well this is a crappy prototype
commentary on the non prototype retail
ones are available at shop not come
another guy this is a crappy prototyping
a panda the band itself is good it has
this like antenna mount which is really
bad I'm so it's blue when I'm disengaged
and then I just pressed this cruise
control button right here you can see
sat so I'll just press it and then back
engaged is driving the car
does it run on Windows Mobile no it runs
on neo s the only operating system I was
going to see certified but I shouldn't
say it's not certified for anything it's
a crappy part of Android if you have to
flip and redo the Mount know you don't
do recalibrate calibrations the same
we-we-we we dealt with that we dealt
with port in your calibrations they're
fine my car needs maintenance I'm sure
it does Grove new convert inspiration
now I wasn't impressed
y'all test it and snow yeah bucks and
stuff I wouldn't use it when there's
snow on the road just like any other
cruise control system but people think
like this is like something that matters
in software in cars it's not
face it's the one plus three Oh the
triangle is just um the car in front of
you so it shows if it's detecting on a
lead car in front of you that's what
that that's what that red triangle
surrounded by the yellow is how much
data does the service user oh you wait
I'll wait the data patch I'll give you
guys something I'll write the data patch
um so if you say only upload over Wi-Fi
it won't use much data anymore that term
is solid all these things are good throw
out a type e on throat earth API lurks I
don't have to we'll have to go home and
we'll have to check the quality of the
data kill the wobble you won't put your
dough with the wobble I don't think the
Civic wobbles sounds perfect to
supercruise but I feel like the Civic
drives just as well as I do
Toyota might have a little wobble
particularly tall Toyota's like the rav4
well the Prius has tons of wobble well
that's just because the Prius is
actuators crappy but I'm very happy with
this
made up of data speed bandwidth uh sorry
it's not really going to the internet
guys you don't actually think Corolla
non-typical is a little bit better yeah
we have a global map not a big global
yeah we're building a global HD map it's
being built right now by the end of the
year at the end of the other maps are
gonna be out and we're gonna of course
give it away for free
guess what you guys back to look
so cruising at a nice gentle 42 miles an
hour he will be coming in for a stop
behind this car notice how it detects
the car and it sees that triangle right
there that's a you know your gut so
we're gonna come to a nice stop in this
car good job open pylons the green is
the currently oh yeah rav4 doing full
speed yeah I could do that let's stormy
life go we accelerate no look it's
accelerating faster good job whoever did
that only controls team in the car now
I'm very happy with acceleration was
cruising down the street with my six
phone
all right so now we're getting a little
bit too suburban II hear what you got
back in the mouth and flip you around
what's with the tape oh I don't know
these are Prototype cars
does it know how to drive stick no it
does not but it is open source so if you
want to write that and like build an
actuator you actually probably can't
really can build a little servo thing
but your Chooch a new rap track I don't
know man
but that too much time for rapping
lately so this is the fusion problem
fusing with lead cars that are stopped
so I had to intervene there if you press
either gas or the brake pedal the system
disengages how do you make money if it's
open source we get money from VCS no
kidding I'm kidding B C's we have a shop
where we sell hardware that's compatible
with our ecosystem check out shop comma
dot ai
cruising by the police
I'm over rear view mirror in this car I
just have me you but I think is legal I
got pulled over once within yawn
and the cop asked what it was and I said
it's dashcam the cops like oh cool he's
like you look like an upstanding citizen
I'm not gonna write you a ticket it was
really because I was driving a Prius
if you drive cheap cars you're less
likely to give tickets I use the drive
expensive cars they always give me
pickets like come on man I Drive a Prius
come on chef that coming that AI is how
we make money we are a hardware startup
we sell hardware like badger no I didn't
get pulled over for anything related to
that I got pulled over night my lights
off this was the second day I got the
Prius and I forgot that the lights were
not automatic officer pulled me over at
news I was drinking I was like no
officer like it's a new car it's the
second day I had it means like what is
that like a dashcam that's what we do we
make dash cams we sell them at shop that
comes that I you should check it out put
one of your cruising I didn't say that I
should chill to the police we are hiring
we're absolutely hiring I give me a job
at comedy I is the email for that you
can check out our hiring page coming on
air slash hiring we're not pretentious
enough to call anything careers careers
spend 20 years we're gonna solve
self-driving cars and two and a half so
get an early on that all right
does this car have a huge comment on it
nah now where's stealth mode bro like if
you watch these periscopes you know what
we're up to
but like we did like funding shelter the
police right so saying please needy on
tonight put an eon in your cruiser think
about how many hands you'll have for
doughnut-eating who donuts
double-fisting bro with it yawn no no it
sounds like it'd be too much
bureaucratic paperwork to sell to the
police
um and I love doughnuts too so you know
this match is copying I love doughnuts
too I thought it's a delicious I would
eat a doughnut right now if I had a
doughnut nope
so to bed oh so this doesn't work on a
commercial truck now bro what is own
path zero point four point four that is
the latest release of open pilot and you
can see open pilot right here running on
my crappy prototype a yawn yeah I know
please shoot I live by yeah follow
perpetrator mode is it legal to have no
hands on the wheel where I live
yes as long as you are paying attention
and in control of the vehicle there's no
legal requirement but I do I mean you
guys can't see it on the periscope but I
keep a hand pretty close to the wheel
down here while open pilots driving wait
till you get pulled over by a
self-driving police the one from the
self-driving police Neos yeah oh I
didn't even think about Neos you don't
want to do any more get an e on just
just ya know the up new update won't
work on no and yes
very sensitive we're good we're good for
nighttime driving it'll read stoplights
and everything well
oh let's not ship yet um how is
self-raising cars pretty good pretty
good you can actually check we posted a
Cabana link if you go on our if you're
going to Twitter neo depreciation last
week Neos are over if you're still out
there driving on a neo we have the neo
de on upgrade program we did get second
place we lost by one second but only
could stay at an Acura and we had a
pre-assessment one were cool but yeah I
know if you saw the Neo out there make
sure to get on that neo Dion upgrade for
dollars I don't know what you say a
question mark the problem is things go
yes pandas have api's pandas are
completely open-source we have an API in
Python and we just launched panda Jas
which is a JavaScript API for
interacting with with if your relative
needs a dash cam tell them to go to
Walmart and buy one for $40 to be honest
I'm an honest person how many locks
swimming lines of code for what for a
pot don't we run slop count on it
not that many
yeah if you're looking for like an
easy-to-use dashcam click til fighting
on this you need a herbal come to
California is legal bra
I know right the Colorado really caught
on that really started that train I
don't know if you had a medical card in
California that was always pretty nice
as well oh don't drug test don't be
coming to work fucked up you'll get
fired your dash cams for periscope
broadcasting they probably should
Wow just to think the company's drug
test that's crazy
that's crazy to think about
smoke weed is coming I don't smoke we
didn't drive a car guys do you feel it's
probably better than drinking to driving
a car but still they'll do it
waiting for my car accident thanks brah
I play music through the car speakers
absolutely you don't have bluetooth you
can just pair it oh that's another thing
zero for for ads you can now get to
settings you can now get to settings
without having to go to the Y on
periscope support yeah no no no it's
still turret now it's pulling you really
not don't drink and drive call it uber
or lyft if you don't like uber wow that
was really close to me I'm driving
all right I think the test of the
prototype was pretty successful
we'll take you guys inside for a little
bit we'll walk through the make sure to
keep the headphone jack
oh we're gonna use the headphone jack -
sure - fighting on now we should have
fun now hey we're Apple we're Apple Bros
oh no yeah the headphone jack is uh
getting me on now